rismedia.com 2015-09-06

# Privacy Policy/Terms & Conditions | RISMedia

### Privacy Policy/Terms & Conditions

RISMedia recognizes the importance of protecting the personal information you provide at Web sites owned and/or controlled by RISMedia Inc. Thus, we maintain the following privacy policy:

1\. We gather the following types of information needed to process your transactions, fulfill your requests and maintain our membership records:

> • Contact information you provide (i.e., personal and business addresses, e-mail address, phone and fax numbers, firm affiliations and titles)

> • Information you volunteer, via applications or surveys (i.e., education, designations, specialties and general demographic data)

2\. We use this information to:

> • Improve and customize the content and layout of our sites and other communications tools, such as RISMedia’s Real Estate magazine online and in print

> • Compile our annual Power Broker Survey & Report

> • Notify you of relevant products and services

> • Notify you of upcoming events and programs

> • Compile specialty directories about which you will be made aware

> • Track usage of our sites

3\. RISMedia does not share, sell or trade e-mail addresses with any unauthorized partners of RISMedia, but may provide you with online informational or marketing messages that have been approved by RISMedia for the purposes described in Part 4 of this policy.

4\. We will not share, sell or otherwise provide other information about you to third parties, except for:

> • Exhibitors at RISMedia’s Leadership Conference trade show for the limited purpose of contacting you one time immediately before and after trade shows, through marketing vehicles approved by RISMedia.

> • Our Annual Power Broker Survey and Report: By participating in the survey the participant agrees that in return for recognition of their ranking, the information provided will be made available in print, online and for purchase as part of our Annual Power Broker Report. RISMedia is not responsible for how said information is used by purchasers of the report. We do encourage purchasers to offer participants a way to Opt-Out of their solicitations.

> • When required by law or valid legal process, or to protect the personal safety of our members or the public

> • Some or all of the data collected during promotions or contests on our sites that are sponsored by third parties may be shared with the sponsor for the limited purpose of a one-time marketing follow-up by the sponsor. If information about you will be shared with a sponsor you will be notified prior to your participation in the promotion or contest and you can decide not to participate in the promotion or contest.
> 
> • To offer subscribers participation or enrollment in value-added, complimentary partner offerings.

5\. Credit card information that you and credit authorizers provide when you make payments by credit card or electronic check for products, registrations or other services via RISMedia’s Web site will only be used to process the transactions you request. This information will be provided to and maintained by reputable credit reporting databases, but will never be sold, shared or provided to other third parties.

6\. We use a strict Opt-Out policy for sending online notifications regarding services, products and programs. You may opt out of our Daily e-News by selecting the unsubscribe feature at the bottom of the Daily e-News e-mail or by e-mailing online@rismedia.com.

7\. Some of our sites contain advertising placed by advertising networks pursuant to agreements between RISMedia and the advertising network. We do not control these advertising networks, the sites of third parties reached through links on our site or their information collection practices and RISMedia will not be responsible for the activities of these third parties. The advertising network uses cookies to collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you click on the banner ads appearing on our sites. This information is collected by the advertising network for purposes of measuring and reporting on the advertising to advertisers and RISMedia. The advertising network may also aggregate the information for certain other statistical and reporting purposes.

8\. All content submitted to RISMedia for publication is considered proprietary to RISMedia and may be used in any of its products and services, including but not limited to RISMedia’s websites, e-newsletters, content licensing or membership-based network platforms including RISMedia’s Real Estate Information Network® (RREIN), Top 5 in Real Estate Network, RISMedia’s Housecall and REsource Real Estate Content Solutions.

At any time, RISMedia may store, resize, modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, reproduce, transfer, access or remove submitted content for any purpose that RISMedia considers necessary, in its sole discretion. Those submitting content will be solely responsible for providing accurate information and guaranteeing RISMedia’s use of content will not infringe on any third party rights. RISMedia will not provide compensation for submitted content. RISMedia may use the content as necessary, in the opinion of RISMedia, for the promotion of its websites and services.

9\. All content published on RISMedia.com is property of and copyrighted to RISMedia, Inc. and the Relocation Information Service, Inc. and may not be used in any way or reprinted without the expressed written permission from RISMedia. Any unauthorized use of content published on RISMedia.com will be subject to prosecution and the user will be liable for any damages that occur as a result. Unauthorized use of the RISMedia.com website, content, or our systems, including, but not limited to, unauthorized entry into our systems, misuse of passwords or misuse of any other information, is strictly prohibited. Access to and use of password protected and/or secure areas of the website is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized persons attempting to access these areas of the website may be subject to prosecution. You may not use the website or the content in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, or impair any RISMedia website or service or interfere with any other party’s use and enjoyment of the website or the content. You shall not introduce, nor permit any person to introduce into the website or content, any code or malicious or hidden mechanisms that would impair the operation of the website or content, or of cur computers, networks, or other devices or software. We reserve the right to disable any unauthorized links or frames and specifically disclaims any responsibility for the content available on any other websites linked to our website.

10\. RISMedia, Inc. sweepstakes and/or contests (e.g., RIS Reader Rewards, #RISReaderRewards) are open only to individual legal residents of the 50 United States of America and the District of Columbia who, at the time of entry, are age 18 or older. RISMedia reserves the right to promote all sweepstakes and/or contests using any of its services or products, including, but not limited to, RISMedia’s websites, e-newsletters and social media networks.

All information submitted through sweepstakes and/or contests will be treated in accordance with our Privacy Policy. RISMedia takes perpetual, irrevocable ownership of all sweepstakes and/or contest entries upon submission. By submitting an entry, you hereby authorize RISMedia to use it in any of its services or products, including future articles, promotions or advertisements.

Sweepstakes and/or contest participants will not be required to purchase or otherwise provide payment to enter or claim and/or receive a prize. Prizes are not transferable or divisible. No substitutions or cash equivalents are permitted.

If sweepstakes and/or contest winners fail to provide contact information within seven (7) business days of notification, or are deemed ineligible to participate, their prize will be forfeited and another participant may be selected as a winner.

RISMedia reserves the right to cancel sweepstakes and/or contests at any time, for any reason, without notice. Except where prohibited by law, each participant agrees that any and all disputes, claims and causes of action in response to RISMedia sweepstakes and/or contests will be resolved without resort to litigation.
